(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-06T02:05:50.222762",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Aaah, the good old days
Ah, the good old days,
when I was performing with my friends at the jazz club.
It was so much fun!
Everyone was having their best time dancing, singing, and just having the best time of their life.
Everyone was having the best time dancing, singing, and just living their best lives.
Good memories.
Now I kinda wanna watch old tapes...
Now I kind of want to watch old tapes...
Hmm...
Not this one.
Not this...
Okay, this one. Yeah yeah yeah!
This one was a blast.
I had so much fun on this one!
Oooh...
Ooh...
Ha - ha - hey - yeah, ohh...
Ha-ha-hey-yeah, ohh...
You make me wanna get up in the morning
You make me wanna stay up all night long
You make me wanna get up to be dancing
You make me wanna reach up to the sky, I feel so high
When I first met you, I already knew, something special...
a love unlike I never knew before
was it in your eyes
feelings you can't disguise
something telling me that destiny
knocked on my front door
it's better to believe
than to let by
the happiness I feel inside
don't let go
energy to feel the same
let passion grow
any gets better day
by day
you make me wanna get up in the morning
you make me wanna stay up all night long
you make me wanna get up to be dancing
you make me wanna reach up to the sky
I feel so high
universal love
from heaven above
fundamentally the truth
I've been searching for
secret rendezvous
in my dreams me and you
brand new feelings warmed my soul
like a blaze more and more
like a shield protecting me from night
your love makes me forget those times
I was alone
there's nothing that can touch me
oh oh the beauty of this love
to the world
you make me wanna get up in the morning
you make me wanna stay up all night long
you make me wanna get up to be dancing
you make me wanna reach up to the sky
I feel so high
you make me wanna get up in the morning
you make me wanna stay up all night long
you make me wanna get up to be dancing
you make me wanna reach up to the sky
I feel so high
can you feel this energy
synchronizing you and me
power of positivity
your electricity
it's better to believe
than to let by
the happiness I feel inside
don't let go
energy to feel the same
let passion grow
any gets better day
by day
you make me wanna get up in the morning
you make me wanna stay up all night long
you make me wanna get up to be dancing
you make me wanna reach up to the sky
I feel so high
you make me wanna get up in the morning
you make me wanna stay up all night long
you make me wanna get up to be dancing
you make me wanna reach up to the sky
I feel so high
dance break let's go
yeah
Yay!
Hello everyone!
Welcome to Jazzeta.
Welcome to my birthday party, sorry. Sorry, I want to ri-
Ah, welcome to Jazzeta!
If you guys are watching, Jazzeta is something I've always been dreaming of. I've always wanted to perform and set to big stage like this.
How did you like it?
Um, the moves had a bit of hip-hop, um dance moves in it. Was it cool? Was it cool? Was it cool? Was it cool?
Um, yeah. So,
last time I was also in a jazz club as well,
but this is special because tonight's performance - I was saying tonight, tonight, tonight? Today's performance is all jazz.
So yeah, I hope you liked that one. It's very groove-
Ooh, ooh, if you guys like this,
so, yeah, um,
don't go anywhere because there will be the next performance, right, Buzzle?
don't go anywhere because there will be
the next performance, right, Buzzle?
Buzzle, bu-, Buzzle can't answer, so.
Jadi, masih ada lanjut. Performance berikutnya, Sugi no?
So, there's more. The next performance is...
Kyokou wa ne,
Today, um,
do you guys know?
Do you guys know?
Can you guess? Can you have a little bit of a guess?
I'll guess, um, okay, okay. I'll give you guys some clue.
I'll guess... um, okay, okay.
I'll give you guys some clues.
Hmm. Hmm, huh. We have a special guest.
Hmm... Hmm, huh.
We have a special guest.
So, who can it be? Dadi, dat oh.
Can you guess who?
花が寝る夜 波に映った星
As flowers rest, the waves reflect stars,
うねる月が 足をくすぐる
The waxing moon tickles my feet.
流れる光に 沿って 行って みたら
If I follow the flowing light and look,
耳にささやいた 君に届くかな
Will it reach you who whispered in my ear?
今 手をつないでも
Even if we hold hands now,
精一杯 抱きしめてみても
Even if I embrace you with all my might,
指先でゆらゆらと その動きが
My fingertips sway, and that movement
止まった時計の針に 踏み込んだ
Stepped onto the hands of a stopped clock.
固まった願いさえ 離れた今は
Even frozen wishes are far away now,
その笑顔を知ってるよ
And I know that smile.
光歌う 夜目に映った空
The singing light and sky reflected in night eyes,
さわやかな 香りがくすぐる
A refreshing scent tickles my senses.
足跡を 合わせて 歩いて みたら
If I walk matching our footsteps,
私を見ていた 君に届くかな
Will it reach you who was looking at me?
ずっと手をつないでも
Even if we hold hands forever,
君について行ってみても
Even if I try following after you,
空は雨に染まるんだ
The sky gets dyed in rain.
君を呼び出した 声の形が
The shape of the voice calling out for you
乾いた色を 濡らして
Wets the dry colors,
強く叫んだ声が 散らばった今は
And now that my shouted voice has scattered,
その言葉を知ってるよ
I know those words.
君はわかってるから 教えてくれた
Because you understand, you taught me,
戻らない その幸せは
That happiness that won't return...
I'm so excited to sing this with you!
Thank you so much! Ina has been one of my favorite songs.
Violet has been one of my favorite songs.
So I'm really happy that I got to sing this especially with you!
So I'm really happy to sing this especially with you!
And in Jazzy version as well!
And in a jazzy version as well!
I love jazz and I love you!
Thank you, Ina, and thank you for inviting me to sing with you, especially Violet too!
Thank you, Ina, for inviting me to sing Violet with you!
Inoseta, I also really love your singing voice, so I'm really happy that you want to sing Violet with me!
I really love your singing voice too, so I'm so glad you wanted to sing Violet with me!
Thank you again, love you too, Jazzeta!
重なる夜波に写った星
Stars reflected in the overlapping night waves
片隅から消えてゆく
Fading away from the corner
指先で夜な揺らと
Flickering gently at my fingertips
その動きが止まった時計の
That movement... into the stopped clock's
針に踏み込んだ雲が描いた列車
hands stepping forward, a train drawn by clouds
その笑顔を知ってるよ
I know that smile
ララバランバラランバラン
La la baran bararan baran
ララバランバラランバランチャラランダ
La la baran bararan baran chararanda
ララバランバランバラランダ
La la baran baran bararanda
OH! What's this tape?
I don't think I've seen it before.
Wait, let me play it!
今宵お邪魔を致します
Tonight, I will intrude upon you.
一つ秘密を増やしましょう
Let's add one more secret.
あなたが悪い 心はホテリ
It's your fault my heart is burning.
後悔の先に佇わ 奪えよう 今宵
Standing beyond regret, let's steal it tonight.
唇優しく重ねましょう
Let's gently press our lips together.
指先はそっと肌に合わせましょう
Let's softly match our fingertips to skin.
高鳴る遠い身体の踊り
The thumping dance of distant bodies
叶わないバナナのような私を上げて
Lift up someone like me who can never be fulfilled
エレジーが声落ちてゆけ そこまで骨の髄まで愛するなら
Let the elegy's voice fall, if you love me to the bone
一時なら恐れよして
Put aside your fears for a moment
愛など見当もない癖に
Even though you have no sense of love at all
狙い定め向こう側へ向かいましょう
Aiming straight, let's head to the other side
しなやかな腰でほら
With a supple waist, see?
無理だとか言わないで 進もう
Don't say it's impossible, let's move forward
見つめてみて あの人の笑顔
Look closely at that person's smile
もっとそばで 感じるためにも
To feel it even closer
Let's get up & down
Run for your life!!
鏡の中の自分見つめて プラス思考で
Look into your reflection in the mirror, with positive thinking
Run for your life!!
そうバラ色の私になるの! そう信じて!
Yes, I'll become a rose-colored me! Believe it!
Hey Hey ! Can you look at my honey?
Hey Hey! Can you look at my honey?
みてみて!
Look, look!
やばいまた目があった! 抑えきれない
Oh no, our eyes met again! I can't hold it back
Oh my baby! ほかの子なんて嫌!!見ないで
Oh my baby! I don't want any other girl!! Don't look at them
あたしのほうがいいんだから
It's definitely better with me!
Hold on!
暗い顔しないで 顔あげて
Don't make a gloomy face, lift up your head
笑顔でそうよ Cheese & Cheese & Smile!
With a smile, yes, Cheese & Cheese & Smile!
自分らしくやれれば それでいいから
If you do it your own way, that's fine
もっとあなた 独り占めしたい
I want to hog you all to myself more
もっとあなたのこと 満足させるのは あたしだけ
The only one who can satisfy you more is just me
Run for your life!!
鏡の中の自分見つめて プラス思考で
Look into your reflection in the mirror, with positive thinking
Run for your life!!
そうバラ色の私になるの そう信じて
Yes, I'll become a rose-colored me, believe it
もうダメよ あなたの前だと動けないの
No way, right in front of you I can't move
無力のあたしのうえ
On top of my powerlessness
態度にホント悩ませる
I'm really troubled by your attitude
自分のことなのに... 本当後悔...
Even though it's about myself... I really regret it...
毎日 同じ繰り返しだけど
Every day is the same repetition, but
きっとひとりひとり 意味をもつて生きている
Surely everyone lives with a meaning
誰々が Dreams come true
Everyone's dreams come true
Run for your life!!
鏡の中の自分見つめて プラス思考で
Look into your reflection in the mirror, with positive thinking
Run for your life!!
そうバラ色の私になるの そう信じて
Yes, I'll become a rose-colored me, believe it
Run for your life!!
鏡の中の自分見つめて プラス思考で
Look into your reflection in the mirror, with positive thinking
Run for your life!!
そうバラ色の私になるの そう信じて
Yes, I'll become a rose-colored me, believe it
Run for your life!!
あなたの声が あなたの色が あたし埋め尽くす
Your voice, your color, fills me up
Run for your life!!
今夜はききっと 忘れられない夜になるから
Tonight will surely become an unforgettable night
Hi! How's the performance?
It was fall, right? Fall, fall, fall, falling.
It was pretty good, it was really cool. I...
I tried my best to use my tiptoes for that one. Hope you guys liked it. FesTia made an appearance.
どうさ、かっこよかったよね? どうさ、も、そう、Fwiking cool!
How was it? Pretty cool, right? It was so freaking cool!
I had so much fun singing with her. Oh well.
Don't forget, um, actually not don't forget. Actually, we still have a little bit of something.
Last time we had the tamin, a bottle, but today, we have many, many cool stuff. We have more cool stuff even cooler than tatamin, what could it be?
Last time we had Tatamin, a bottle, but today, we have many, many cool stuff. We have more cool stuff even cooler than Tatamin, what could it be?
パヤキラキラ まだだよぎにー
Pyachiki-rakira, masih terlalu gini.
Tada!
Wow, tentu saja,
bukan birthday party kalau tidak iklan dulu, ya enggak?
Kita iklan dulu, guys. This is my merchandise!
Good zu!
Isn't it really beautiful? I really love the dress.
Do I do I do I look nice? Otona poi ne.
Do I look nice? Otonappoi ne.
This is like, just like imagine like a spy going inside a ballroom having a glass of a strawberry juice. The concept is like jazz, but also like spy, kind of like mix together.
So, yeah! Aruteramama, arigatou!
Thank you so much for making such a beautiful illustration.
So, of course, if you see here, it's very rare that my theme is like red because you know if you see in the back, I mean the stage, everything everything is super red.
So, I hope you guys like this one. And there's still more, there's still more, there's still more.
Okay, let's see the items one by one. First one, hai!
Oh, a diorama acrylic stand. Acrylic stand tokka.
これいいな。これはに置けるで メジャ。どこに置けるで。どこに置けるで。どこに置ける、どこに、どこに、どこに、どこに、どこに...
This is so good. Where can you put this? On your desk, dining table, anywhere you like!
Viga, guys! Gila, keren banget acrylic stand.
Look, guys! This acrylic stand is so cool.
Beautiful, kalian bisa taruh di mana aja.
Beautiful! You can put this anywhere.
You can have, you can have elegant, elegant Zeta accompany you in your room.
You can have an elegant Zeta accompany you in your room,
Or you can bring this around. I usually bring my acrylic stand inside like a pouch.
or you can bring this around. I usually bring my acrylic stand inside a pouch.
So, if you find like an accessory for the pouch, it would be nice.
So if you find an accessory for the pouch, it would be nice.
And it's something like... um, it says...
"Fancy a dance with me?" Question mark. Ooh, fancy, fancy, super fancy!
Hai, sugi, next!
Okay, next!
Whoa, it's a hoodie!
So this is something, you guys... I feel like you guys want it for a long time. Cuz you guys were always like, "Zeta, can you make us something to wear?" And now we have a uniform!
So this is something, you guys... I feel like you guys wanted it for a long time, 'cause you guys were always like, "Zeta, can you make us something to wear?" And now we have a uniform!
Jangan kasih tahu kalau misalkan lu geting up punya seragam. Tapi ini bukan seragam ya, ini kayak cozy gitu loh kayak...
Don't tell anyone that you guys are getting a uniform. But this isn't a uniform, you know, it's like a cozy kind of...
Enak, kalau mau di rumah santai, kalau mau keluar juga bisa. Soalnya enggak terlalu formal, tapi enggak terlalu casual banget ya, in between, kalian bisa pakai.
comfy, if you want to relax at home or go outside, you can. Because it's not too formal, but not too casual either—in between, you can wear it.
Ini hoodienya lumayan oversized ya, tapi ini comfy banget. This is so good.
This hoodie is quite oversized, but it's super comfy. This is so good.
Yeah, kakak-kakak, silakan dibeli. Kakak-kakak, ya, ini aduh bahannya halus, ya.
Yeah, big bros and sisters, please buy it. Big bros and sisters, yeah, the material is so smooth.
Udah gitu, apalagi nih? Ada gambar ilustrasinya di belakang. Uh, cantik sekali! Uh, langsung checkout.
And what else? There's an illustration on the back. Ooh, so pretty! Ooh, go ahead and check out right away.
Yeah, this is beautiful. Look at that illustration. Lucu, di show?
Yeah, this is beautiful. Look at that illustration. Isn't it cute?
So the main point of this illustration is Zeta with like BaZeta's suit, actually. If you look at it, yeah,
and it's gray, so we know it's, we know it's Zeta because it's gray.
and it's gray, so we know it's Zeta because it's gray.
Anyways, yeah, and then it has a little bit of tag in it, and the tags say "Vestia Zeta". So, yeah, this is what it looks like.
Anyways, yeah, and then it has a little tag in it, and the tag says "Vestia Zeta". So, yeah, this is what it looks like.
Yeah, you can wear this in conventions, or meet and greet, or wherever you want to go. Honestly, it's not tacky at all, so wear it wherever.
Yeah, you can wear this to conventions, meet and greets, or wherever you want to go. Honestly, it's not tacky at all, so wear it wherever!
Okay, next!
Oh! It's a pocket size BaZeta plushie keychain! So cute!
Oh! It's a pocket-size BaZeta plushie keychain! So cute!
Wait, that's actually so cute. That's so cute. That's... oh!
That's like the drawing in um in the back of the hoodie, but except it's now in a plushie. Yay!
That's like the drawing on the back of the hoodie, but except it's now a plushie! Yay!
So we have BaZeta plushie, we have um the other Zeta plushie, the friends one, and now we have the pocket-size. Keren banget, lucu!
So we have the BaZeta plushie, we have the other Zeta plushie, the friends one, and now we have the pocket-size. It's so cool and cute!
It's like you can bring this to travelling... liburan gitu. Kalau ketai, kalau ini nih, seret ikh te...
It's like you can bring this traveling... on vacation. If you want, if you want this...
You can bring this or you can hang it on your bag, or you can have multiple of it and make an Ita bag.
Or, I don't know, this is a keychain, so you can hang this anywhere. Ini bisa digantung di mana aja, mau jadi jimat keberuntungan, mau kalian gantung di celana, di tas, di tembok, di mana aja, di rambut, terserah ya.
Or, I don't know, this is a keychain, so you can hang this anywhere. You can hang this anywhere—want it to be a lucky charm, hang it on your pants, your bag, the wall, anywhere, in your hair, whatever you like!
Ini keren banget. Ini lucu dan ini halus, pokoknya. Kelihatan sih dari fotonya. This is really cute. Dan ini pocket size. Jadi tuh ukurannya lumayan ya guys, kalian bisa baca sendiri ukurannya. Ukurannya lucu.
This is really cool. It's cute and it's soft, basically. You can tell from the photo. This is really cute. And it's pocket-size. So the size is quite nice, guys, you can read the size yourself. The size is cute.
Okay, next!
And this is the last item is Secretary's Pin Me Down Pin Badge! Ooh!
And this is the last item, Secretary's Pin Me Down Pin Badge! Ooh!
So this is a badge as a secretary, so I wanted something um I wanted like a tie at first, but then I decided on a badge because badge is more wearable.
So this is a badge as a secretary, so I wanted something... um, I wanted like a tie at first, but then I decided on a badge because a badge is more wearable.
So this badge, you can put it, you can wear it um on your shirt, you can wear it on your bags, because you know, people uh wear pins on their bags. You can pin this on your shoe, your socks, wherever.
So this badge, you can put it, you can wear it on your shirt, you can wear it on your bags, because you know, people wear pins on their bags. You can pin this on your shoes, your socks, wherever.
This is really nice um um or so, if you have like the original idea is for it if you have a tie, you can like pin the badge on the tie. Jadi kalau kalian punya dasi, kalian bisa pin di dasi gitu misalnya atau...
This is really nice. And also, if you have... the original idea is for it... if you have a tie, you can pin the badge on the tie. So if you have a necktie, you can pin it on the tie, for example, or...
Kalian bisa pin di mana aja. Aku juga sebenarnya punya nih pin-pin gitu nih. I have a pin as well if you guys can see, I have the deer pin. You can pin it in your um belt, bag if you have that. I mean, I have thigh highs, but yeah, you can pin it anywhere. You can pin it in your shoes if you want and all that or your hair bad, here you have a hair band.
you can pin it anywhere. I actually have these pins too, see? I have a pin as well if you guys can see, I have the deer pin. You can pin it on your belt, bag if you have that. I mean, I have thigh-highs, but yeah, you can pin it anywhere. You can pin it on your shoes if you want and all that, or your hairband—here, you have a hairband.
Any pin, kalian jadi ini serbaguna, oke? Uh, but of course it doesn't end there because I also...
Any pin, so this is versatile, okay? Uh, but of course, it doesn't end there because I also...
I prepared three voice packs for my birthday as well, yay!
So I prepared the stories for the three birthdays as well. I wanted different stories for each language.
So I prepared stories for the three birthdays as well. I wanted different stories for each language.
Semuanya yang bilang skip iklan, kalian enggak bisa skip, karena kita lanjut terus!
For those of you saying "skip ad," you can't skip, because we're going right through!
First one, situational voice in Japanese.
So, kore wa nihongo no voice nanda kedo, the title is "The Runaway Princess Who Found Herself in a Jazz Club."
So, this is a Japanese voice pack, and the title is "The Runaway Princess Who Found Herself in a Jazz Club."
Yay! If you guys are unsure, there is a preview button to sneak peek the content.
Yay! If you guys are unsure, there's a preview button to sneak peek the content.
So, it's it's about a princess from a certain kingdom, she sneaks out of the castle to perform as a jesting at the club.
So, it's about a princess from a certain kingdom, she sneaks out of the castle to perform as a guest singer at the club.
So, this is really interesting.
Next! So, the second one is a different story in English. It's called "A Spy Hired to Track Down a Prince at a Ballroom," when a mysterious man approaches her. Ooh, who could that be?
So, this is about Zeta who infiltrates a ballroom as a spy on a mission searching for the prince she is targeting. Yay!
Next! Lastly, we have something a little bit familiar, maybe you're curious, a different story in Bahasa Indonesia, it's called "Behind the Scenes with a Singer."
Next! Lastly, we have something a little bit familiar, maybe you're curious, a different story in Indonesian, it's called "Behind the Scenes with a Singer."
We, behind the scenes dengan seorang penyanyi. Yeh!
We, behind the scenes with a singer. Yeah!
Jadi story-nya ini tu, ceritanya itu lagi backstage terus dengar-dengar Zeta ngomong. This is if you guys want to hear me yap behind the scenes, basically.
So this story, it's like, the story is backstage and hearing Zeta talk. This is if you guys want to hear me yap behind the scenes, basically.
And the voice pack is sold separately and not included in the full merch set.
Um before before I end before I end this commercial break, I have one more secret to share with you guys. There's a sneak peek of a special bonus you will get from buying the good set. Bam!
Um, before I end this commercial break, I have one more secret to share with you guys. There's a sneak peek of a special bonus you will get from buying the good set. Bam!
Wait, kore ne, this is cheki-style bromide card with a handwritten autograph. So, I'm I'm handwriting it the autograph myself.
Wait, this is a cheki-style bromide card with a handwritten autograph. So, I'm handwriting the autograph myself.
Remember, there is a limited quantity for the cards that are personally signed, so don't miss out.
Remember, there's a limited quantity for the cards that are personally signed, so don't miss out.
You'll you'll get my beautiful autograph, or might not beautiful autograph, whatever. You'll get you'll get a rare one if I if I accidentally misspelled my name or something.
You'll get my beautiful autograph, or maybe not beautiful autograph, whatever. You'll get a rare one if I accidentally misspelled my name or something.
Please check the description for the links and details. You can purchase the merchandise on Hololive Production site at 9:00 PM WIB or 11:00 PM Japan time, or after the streaming ends.
Please check the description for the links and details. You can purchase the merchandise on the Hololive Production site at 9:00 PM WIB or 11:00 PM Japan time, or after the streaming ends.
Or you can just click the link on the pin chat. Yeh!
Or you can just click the link in the pinned chat. Yeah!
Yeah, this will be PO, purchase order. So for more details you should check the homepage. Thank you, that's all, yay!
Silakan skip ad!
Please skip ad!
Have you guys heard of this story?
Once upon a time, there was a girl.
She got lost and she met new friends along the way and went on adventures with them. And... the rest is history.
お話をしよう
Let's tell a story.
昔話よりもっともっと素敵なおとぎ話
A fairy tale even more wonderful than old tales.
ふと目を開けると真っ白なうさぎ
Opening my eyes, I see a pure white rabbit.
大慌てで駆け行く後を追うの
Hurrying off, chasing after it—
チクタク チクタク 急いで行かないと間に合わない!
Tick-tock, tick-tock, if I don't hurry, I won't make it!
ああ チクタク チクタク ギクシャクするのはもう嫌だ
Ah, tick-tock, tick-tock, I'm sick of feeling all out of sync.
そら チクタク チクタク 時間はどんどん減っていく
Look, tick-tock, tick-tock, time is steadily ticking away.
もう兎にも角にも僕には時間がない
Anyway, regardless, I have no time left!
ねえ そんなに慌てて一体全体どうしたの?
Hey, why are you in such a rush? What's wrong?
どこかの誰かといつかどこかで待ち合わせ?
Meeting someone somewhere at some time?
そう! 彼女はチクタクとっても時間にシビアだよ
That's right! She is very strict about time!
そんなに? そうさ! だって彼女は女王様
Really? That's right! Because she's the Queen.
カカクシカジカ チクタクどうにも時間がないから
With all things considered, tick-tock, there's no time at all,
話があるならまたの機会にしておくれない
so if you have something to say, please save it for another time.
それならひとつだけ教えて何故そんなときでも
Then tell me just one thing: why, even at a time like this,
陽気にうたを謳うの?
do you sing so cheerfully?
それはミュージックランド ミュージックランド?
That's Musicland! Musicland?
そうさ ミュージックランド ワンダーランド!
That's right, Musicland, Wonderland!
ここがミュージックランドだからさ! じゃあお先に失礼また会う日までバイバイさようなら!
Because this is Musicland! Well then, excuse me, until we meet again, bye-bye, farewell!
待ってー!
Wait!
ああ なんて不思議な世界なのでしょう
Ah, what a mysterious world this is.
この先は何が待っているのかしら お嬢さん えっ? お嬢さん 私?
What awaits us ahead? Young lady? Eh? Young lady, me?
そうお嬢さん あなたは誰なの? who am i? 問いかけてみよう
Yes, young lady, who are you? Who am I? Let's ask ourselves.
何故? who am i? 分からないんだ
Why? Who am I? I don't know.
who are you? ねえ教えてよ who am i? 曖昧さ
Who are you? Hey, tell me. Who am I? It's so vague.
ただ分かっているのは謳ってる僕は最高にハッピーってこと
All I know is that as I sing, I am supremely happy.
ちっちゃい仕掛けじゃ ちゅっかたもどうにも ちっちゃいさがないから
If the tricks are too small and there's hardly any difference anyway,
話があるなら またのんきにして遅れ
if you have something to discuss, take your time and reply later.
それなら一つだけ教えて なぜそんな時でも 陽気な歌を歌うの
If so, teach me just one thing: why do you sing a cheerful song even at times like that?
それはミュージカル
That is a musical!
ミュージカル そうさ ミュージカル
A musical, that's right, a musical!
ワンダーランド
Wonderland!
ここがミュージカル だからさあ
This is a musical, so come on!
じゃあお先に失礼 またお暇で バイバイさようなら 待って！
Well, excuse me, until next time, bye-bye, farewell—wait!
なんて不思議な 世界なの でしょう
What a mysterious world this is...
この先は 何かが 待っているかしら
What could be waiting for me beyond this point?
お嬢さん え？ お嬢さん
"Young lady?" — "Huh?" — "Young lady!"
私？ そう、お嬢さん
"Me?" — "Yes, young lady."
なに？ 君は誰？ 私の名前は… 君は名前など…
"What? Who are you?" — "My name is..." — "You have no name..."
そういうあなたわ誰なの？
"Then who on earth are you?"
Who am I? 問いかけてみよう 何故？
Who am I? Let me ask myself, why?
Who am I? 分からないんだ
Who am I? I don't really know.
Who are you? ねえ教えてよ
Who are you? Hey, tell me.
Who am I? 曖昧さ
Who am I? Such ambiguity.
誰か分かってるのは 歌ってる僕は 最後にハッピーってこと
Whoever knows, the me who sings is ultimately happy!
You love music 歌を唄えば 少しずつ見えてくる
You love music. As I sing songs, it slowly comes into view.
僕が生きる意味は きっとここにある
The meaning of my life must be right here.
だってそうぼくは そうねきっと私も 最高なsingerなのさ
Because that's me—that's right, I'm sure I'm the ultimate singer too!
この風変わりなリズムはどこから聴こえてくるのかしら
Where could this eccentric rhythm be coming from, I wonder?
そりゃ私よ 私んことだろ？
Well, that's me! You mean me, right?
それは私だよ 私太っ腹ろ さっかくけったら始めるぞ
"That's me! I'm generous, so once we get set, we're starting!"
お茶はいかが？ お茶はいかが？ 楽しく飲めば 世界も踊る
"How about some tea? How about some tea? If you drink happily, even the world dances!"
お茶はいかが？ さあお茶をどうぞ なんだなんて変なプレイバー
"How about some tea? Now, please have some tea." — "My, what a strange player."
ふだんの味になれちまったら すべてがたいがいに なっちまうもろさ
"If you get too used to ordinary flavors, everything becomes frail and fades away."
ありきたりなものじゃつまらない それを知ったヤツらは みんなイカれちまうのさ
"Ordinary things are boring; those who learn that all go crazy."
ありがたりの ものじゃつまらない
"Things that are taken for granted are boring..."
それを知りたい奴は みんなイカれちまうのさ
"...and those who want to know all go crazy."
ほらお茶はいかが？ きゅうていらいたけりゃ いかれちまえ お茶はいかが？ さあお茶をどうぞ
"Come on, how about some tea? If you want to stay courtly, go crazy! How about some tea? Now, have some tea."
さあ イカれる楽しいディタイム
"Now, a wonderfully crazy teatime!"
迷い込んだ 森の中 私を誘う声が 深い霧にこだまする 私の道はどっち
Wandering deep into the forest, a voice inviting me echoes through the thick fog. Which way is my path?
あっち、そっち、それともこっち
"Over there, that way, or perhaps this way?"
ゆうじゅうふだんな お嬢さん だけどそれは私もう同じ あっちもそっちも歩く道
"Indecisive young lady!" — "But that's the same for me, both paths lead on."
あなあ 喜びや 悲しみや 愛しさまで 詠にしたい 今も全部
Ah, joy, sadness, and even affection—I want to weave them all into song, even now.
繰りかえされていたら
As it was repeated over and over,
最初に見つけていたものが 何か分からなくなって
I forgot what it was I first discovered.
最後に残されたものは 透明な退屈を知らない音楽が
And what was left at the end was music that knows no boredom.
光星の残骸 それを芸術と呼べるのか
The debris of starlight, can that be called art?
頭の中はグチャグチャでも 透明なのは悪くない
My head is a mess, but being transparent isn't bad.
だけど決めた 私は決めた 私の道
Still, I decided, I chose my own path.
幸か不幸か 彼女が選んだ
For better or worse, the path she chose
道は女王へ続く道
leads to the Queen.
女王陛下の おなりー！
Her Majesty the Queen arrives!
私 が女王様さ！
I am the Queen!
何か文句あるのか？
Got a problem with that?
美しい歌声 当たり前じゃない？
Isn't a beautiful singing voice obvious?
オーケストラさあ 始めましょう
Orchestra, let's begin!
あなたが女王様 そうよ覚えておき
You're the Queen? Remember that well.
美しい歌声 当たり前じゃない
A beautiful singing voice is only natural.
オーケストラさあ 始めましょう
Orchestra, now let's begin!
私のミュージック
My music!
ピアノ
Piano!
ウッドベース
Wood bass!
ドラムス
Drums!
ブラスセクション
Brass section!
みんな言うことをお聞き 私のために奏でなさい
Everyone listen to what I say, play for my sake!
すべて私のものよ 私は女王様だからさ
Everything is mine, because I am the Queen!
ちょっと待って！
Wait just a minute!
これはみんなで奏でるミュージック
This is music played together by everyone!
へんてこでもまとまらなくても
Even if it's wacky or uncoordinated,
どんなときでもハッピーを感じてるのさ
we feel happy no matter what time it is.
十人十色だけど 重なればハーモニーになる
Everyone is different, but when combined, it becomes harmony.
理由は単純さ だってwe love music!
The reason is simple, because we love music!
お話をしよう 昔話よりもっともっと素敵な おとぎ話
Let's tell a story, a fairy tale far more wonderful than old tales.
それはありふれた魔法のフィロソフィー みんなのハートに隠されたミュージックランド
It's a common magical philosophy, a music land hidden in everyone's heart.
ミュージック
Music!
Alice in musicland
How do you get to music land?
Over the hill or underland? Or just behind the tree?
When clouds go rolling by, they roll away and leave the sky.
Where is the land beyond the eye that people cannot see?
Where do stars go? Where is the silver crescent moon?
They must be somewhere in the sunny afternoon.
Alice in musicland, where is the path to music land?
Over the hill or here or there? I really wonder where.
Now we know the answer...
When we're enjoying music, always we're in music land!
Yay!
Gimana? Gimana? Gimana?
How was it? How was it?
どうでしたか？
How was it?
Oh, I can't believe it's almost ending, almost, because it still hasn't ended, right?
Oh, I can't believe it's almost ending... because it still hasn't ended, right?
How are you guys enjoying it so far? Are you watching it with popcorn? Are you watching it with something else? With coffee?
How are you guys enjoying it so far? Are you watching with popcorn, or something else? With coffee?
Thank you everyone for coming to my birthday party, because, ah, I am so excited, I'm so happy that my, that my vision is coming to reality.
Thank you everyone for coming to my birthday party, because I am so excited... I'm so happy my vision is coming to reality.
Ah, man, that was really nice, huh? That was really nice.
I hope you guys notice my love for all things like retro, vintage, and like jazz, you know? Always like to create something like a little bit different, like slightly old-school.
I hope you guys notice my love for retro, vintage, and jazz, you know? We always like to create something a little different, slightly old-school.
Makasih semuanya yang udah bikin impian aku jadi realita pokoknya.
Thank you everyone for making my dream a reality, really.
Ah, senang banget, eh, pecah... pecah, curi-curi sikit.
Ah, so happy, ah, epic... epic, stealing a little bit.
Arigatou! Thank you to everyone and my guests that made this happen, amazing special guest, and I am happy if you guys just had fun, groove to the music and stuff.
Arigatou! Thank you to everyone and my guests that made this happen, amazing special guests, and I hope you guys had fun grooving to the music.
So, yeah, I hope you guys enjoyed watching it and thank you for always supporting me! With sticker! Arigatou!
So, yeah, I hope you guys enjoyed watching and thank you for always supporting me! With a sticker, arigatou!
Bye-bye!
This will be a moment I will never forget!!
Thank you for all the support & amazing memories!